Despite what everyone tells you online,
getting 100K a month, 200K a month,
Lamborghini SVJ, Porsche GT3 RS,
the real thing that everyone watching this
should
aspire for is an extra $2,000 a month.
And once you find an extra $2,000 a month,
everything changes.
And I don't think we're giving enough
credit to how much of a change that is.
So right here is a graph.
[chuckles] I'm not actually sure
if Declan's managed to
green screen it behind me,
or maybe he's having a tough day in the
edit and he's
just put it in front of you.
But there used to be analytics in
Facebook, which was
my main social media platform,
and this was a snapshot I took the day I
hit
40,000 followers.
This page has now got 1.1 million.
My Insta's got 1.4 million.
TikTok's got 1.8 million.
Sorry, that's an appeal to authority.
You do that to people so they start
listening to what you're saying.
It's why personal trainers get their tops
off when they're talking about stuff.
You subconsciously put their physique
and what they're saying together.
Same reason that business coaches often
sit in their nice car.
But anyway, back to the graph.
Consider this line that's going down the
middle is
20,000 followers. You'll realize
that for almost all of the time, I had
no following. Now,
an interesting thing in this graph is
that this actually started
in 2014.
I passed my PT certification April
2014,
and that was the day I started posting.
Now,
the reason I'm showing you this graph
is to remind you, you are not special.
And I think some of you go through life
maybe a bit disillusioned.
Maybe you listen to too many Steven
Bartlett podcasts, I don't know.
And I posted every single day
and got no growth.
I had so many opportunities to be
frustrated.
And the interesting thing is here,
let's say you meet me in summer 2016.
Let's say August.
You would think I'm fucking mental.
You would say, "All right, mate,
so you've been posting every day for two
years and
you've got 3,000 followers. Cool.
Nice one." Do you know how many online
clients I had? Zero.
Do you know how many things I'd sold?
Zero. You would've thought I was mental.
If you met me a year later in 2017, "Mate,
you're blowing up.
How did you become an overnight success?"